<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Kubernetes - Tag - Sammy</title>
        <link>https://samlane.io/tags/kubernetes/</link>
        <description>Kubernetes - Tag - Sammy</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 13:15:40 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://samlane.io/tags/kubernetes/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Developing Inside Minikube</title>
    <link>https://samlane.io/developing-inside-minikube/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 13:15:40 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://samlane.io/developing-inside-minikube/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://source.unsplash.com/8Gg2Ne_uTcM/1600x900" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Problem Recently I have the need to write code that interacts with kubernetes outside and inside the cluster. Outside is easy I can just execute my application on the host and it sends the requests off to the API. Developing insight would be a pain if everytime I made a change to a line of code I would have to rebuild the container image and redeploy the pod using that new image.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Kubernetes Static IP for Ingress Controller</title>
    <link>https://samlane.io/kubernetes-aws-static-ip-ingress/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 12:30:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://samlane.io/kubernetes-aws-static-ip-ingress/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="https://source.unsplash.com/UrtxBX5i5SE/1600x900" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Introduction and motivation Recently at work I had a requirement to provide clients static IPs for our kubernetes cluster. AWS managed load balancers are fantastic but due to their elastic scale-ability you can not guerentee what IP addresses your load balancer is using. Fortuantly AWS provides the Layer 3 Network LoadBalancer (NLB). The NLB allows for Elastic IPs to attached to it, providing static IPs.
Because we are using an ingress-controller, nginx in this case, a Layer 3 loadbalancer is completely adequate, as the ingress-controller will handle routing to k8s services on the application layer.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
